迈克 · 诺斯: 第二步，你们将从通过测试开始,
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Step 2,
you will start with your tests passing,
你要禁止暗藏的茴香酒。
you will ban implicit anys.
这是一个 tsconfig 编译器选项，noImplicitAny，true。
And this is a tsconfig compiler option,
noImplicitAny, true.
因此，设置为 true 意味着，而不是打字稿回落到任何地方
So setting that to true means, instead of
TypeScript falling back to any in places
如果它不能通过推理解决问题，它就会向你抛出一个错误。
where it can't figure things out through
inference, it will throw an error at you.
不抛出一个错误，但它会给你一个编译错误。
Not throw an error but
it will give you a compile error.
迈克 · 诺斯: 那么你就会有一个基本的待办事项清单
&gt;&gt; Mike North: So you're gonna then have
basically a to-do list, and it's mostly
隐式 anys 组成，现在已经变成了编译错误。
going to consist of implicit anys that
now have turned into compile errors.
你们要尽可能提供有意义的类型,
And you are gonna go through and
provide meaningful types where you can,
如果你不能，你可以使用一个明确的“任何”。
and where you can't,
you'll use an explicit any.
你可以添加一个类型注释，这是一个 any,
You'll add a type annotation saying,
this is an any,
我明确地说，这里什么都行。
I am explicitly saying,
whatever is fine here.
这是一个很好的时间来强调明确的类型,
This is a good time for
me to highlight DefinitelyTyped,
这是一个提供环境类型信息的开源项目，对吗？
which is an open source project that
provides ambient type information, right?
这就像 DTS 文件一样。
This is like the DTS files.
它提供单独的 npm 包，您可以带入，理想情况下，它将完美
It provides separate npm packages that you
can bring in and it'll, ideally, perfectly
在你习惯使用的基础 JavaScript 代码基础之上。
lay on top of the underlying JavaScript
code base that you're used to using.
例如，如果要使用 Lodash，则
For example,
if you want to use Lodash, which
除非最近发生了什么变化，否则这不是用打字稿写的。
unless something has changed recently,
that is not written in TypeScript.
它是用常规的 JavaScript 编写的。
It's written in regular JavaScript.
您可以导入 Lodash 类型，以及
You can import the Lodash types, and
你会从输入代码中得到所有的好处。
you'll get all of the benefits
that you get from typed code.
但是它真的很像实现
But it's really like
the implementation and
然后把类型信息放在上面。
then the type information
laying on top of it.
打印出来的出版物，成千上万的图书馆和
DefinitelyTyped publishes out
to thousands of libraries and
它们都在 npm 包作用域中输入或输入类型。
they all are in the npm package
scope at typed or at types.
所以你会看到在类型斜杠粗线。
So you'll see at types slash lodash.
如果你看一下这个工作坊项目的 JSON 包,
And if you look in the package
JSON on this workshop project,
我想您将在类型斜杠节点中看到。
I think you'll see at types slash node.
这里有 fs 模块和 path 模块,
So that has the fs module and
the path module,
所有的类型信息都在这里，对吗？
all the type information there, right?
所以现在是一个很好的时机，开始把它作为一种
So this is a good time to sort of
start bringing that in as a way of
与这些暗藏的杀手作斗争。
combating these implicit anys.
然后你就可以让你的测试再次通过
And then you're going to get
your test passing again, and
这是第二次独立民意调查。
this is a second independent poll request.